# ——• CAYDEN WELTER •—

# CONTACT



caydenwelter@gmail.com



LinkedIn



www.caydenwelter.com

# ABOUT ME

I am currently a Data Science & Computer Science student attending UW-Madison. I am planning to major in Data Science and obtain a certificate in Computer Science and expect to graduate in May of 2024. During my time at UW-Madison and MATC, I have taken many classes in computer science, data visualization/data wrangling, mathematics, and database design/querying. I have professional experience with Microsoft T-SQL and data safety in my business intelligence internship. In my free time, I enjoy working on personal projects and riding my motorcycle.

## SKILLS

- Java & C#
- Python
- Data visualization
- Ability to pick up other programming languages quickly
- PowerShell
- Linux/Unix/Bash
- Windows 10/11
- Microsoft Office products
- Ticketing systems, such as Zendesk
- Jira & Confluence

# **EDUCATION**

## UW - Madison

2022-2024 (expected) | GPA: 3.76

I am majoring in Data Science with a certificate in Computer Science.

# Madison Area Technical College (MATC)

2020-2022 | GPA: 3.92

I spent the first 2 years of my bachelor's degree at MATC and transferred the credits to UW-Madison

## EXPERIENCE

## Business Intelligence Intern at *University of Wisconsin Foundation*

May 2023-Present

Utilized Microsoft T-SQL to facilitate communication list requests and generate ad-hoc information for internal and campus personnel, extracting data from a robust relational database to support the advancement of the University of Wisconsin-Madison while prioritizing data safety.

#### Information Technology Intern at *University of Wisconsin Foundation*

March 2022-May 2023

Collaborated with a team to provide comprehensive day-to-day support to approximately 400 internal employees, addressing hardware, software, account, and other troubleshooting needs. Demonstrated proficiency in Microsoft Powershell by completing many projects utilizing it, including a system for auditing the organization's 3000+ IT assets, and a user-friendly Powershell script with a GUI to automate the provisioning of accounts for new employees.

## Retail Salesworker at Kwik Trip

September 2020-March 2022

Excelled in a fast-paced and dynamic retail environment, providing exceptional guest service as a cashier while maintaining a clean and organized store, and contributed to the kitchen's efficiency and quality standards in a fast-paced environment.

### Shift Lead/Keyholder at Ace Hardware DeForest

October 2019-September 2020

Opened and closed the store during manager absences, ensuring a smooth transition of operations. Handled customer complaints as they arose and handled cash securely.